Speaking: github.com/ValarieR/Speakers-Bio

Phone: +1.678.983.7867 Email: valarie.regas@gmail.com



# VALARIE REGAS DEVOPS & EVANGELISM

## **SUMMARY**

I am a DevOps Engineer, Developer Advocate, and accomplished Tech community speaker, seeking a new adventure! After four years of strictly technical roles, I have shifted into a community-focused position. My ideal role would make use of my public speaking acumen, ability to talk to anyone, and love of ensuring success for both customers, and teammates.

### **PASSIONS**

- CI/CD
- Automation
- Supporting engineers
- Public speaking
- Documenting new processes

Website: ValarieRegas.com

- Teaching & Mentoring
- Project management
- Customer success
- Efficiency

#### **EDUCATION BACKGROUND**

Georgia Tech Coding Boot Camp Georgia Institute of Technology 2017 - 2018

B.A. Psychology, Gender StudiesUniversity of West Georgia 2003 - 2008

#### PUBLIC SPEAKING

30+ past engagements

Scan the QR code to see "Rebuilding Together." Keynote, Connect.tech, 2021



## **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

Developer Advocate | StarTree | 2022 - Present

- Travel extensively to deliver conference sessions and keynotes, raising awareness of Apache Pinot
- Deliver entertaining and informative sessions, to engage the developer community
- · Advocate for mental health in the tech community, and champion self-care among developers

#### DevOps Engineer | Salesforce | 2021 - 2022

- As a part of the managed package team, I deploy quality code often and efficiently
- Maintain thoroughly tested CI/CD pipelines for priority managed packages
- Streamlined the process of other teams making ad hoc requests of the DevOps Bouncers by creating a Slack workflow to triage incoming requests
- Automate manual processes at every available opportunity to increase team efficiency

#### DevOps Engineer | Airbus | 2018 - 2021

- Worked diligently to deliver clean, quality code via CI/CD
- Traveled extensively to speak at conferences; engaged the tech community with Airbus Aerial's drone-focused innovations
- Managed our product's GCP instances, as well as our Jenkins pipelines; deployed automatically to GCP utilizing Docker and Kubernetes